hello there welcome to our insurance
channel
do you wonder why car insurance does not
pay you a claim
well having car insurance make you feel
secure with upcoming loss and financial
damages
but the unknown is the fact that your
claim for your car insurance can be
disapproved
the possible reasons might be an
accurate application
not disclosing the use of your car your
claim falls into the wrong category
the claim does not meet the criteria or
you haven't kept your belongings safe
therefore insurance companies are here
for you to provide the best policies
your only duty is to carefully
understand all the policies
the requirements and ask for more
explanations for future claims
by doing such you can be on the safe
side
to learn more about car insurance and
its policies
thank you for watching